import { v4 as uuidv4 } from "uuid";

export const dummyQuiz = [{
  category:{
  quizTitle:"Quiz on Space Agencies and Centers in India",
  quizDetail:"This quiz level is hard . so are you ready ? You have 10 seconds to answer each question. The faster you answer, the higher your score. When you are done, try again to beat your best score!",
  quiz :[ { 
    id: uuidv4(),
    question:"The day on which the Sun ’ s direct rays cross the celestial equator is called:",
    optionOne:"The Aphelion",
    optionTwo:"The Solstice",
    optionThree:"The Equinox",
    optionFour:"The Ecliptic",
    answer:"The Equinox"
},{ 
    id: uuidv4(),
    question:"Who invented the telescope ?",
    optionOne:"Johannes Kepler",
    optionTwo:"Galileo",
    optionThree:"Hypatia",
    optionFour:"Hans Lippershey",
    answer:"Galileo"
},{ 
    id: uuidv4(),
    question:"Which of these objects is the farthest from the Sun ?",
    optionOne:"Saturn",
    optionTwo:"Neptune",
    optionThree:"90377 Sedna",
    optionFour:"Kuiper belt",
    answer:"Neptune"
},{ 
    id: uuidv4(),
    question:"What term describes the alignment of three celestial bodies?",
    optionOne:"syzygy",
    optionTwo:"sizzle",
    optionThree:"symbology",
    optionFour:"suzerainty",
    answer:"syzygy"
},{ 
    id: uuidv4(),
    question:"What is the smallest planet in the solar system by mass?",
    optionOne:"Earth",
    optionTwo:"Mercury",
    optionThree:"Mars",
    optionFour:"Jupiter",
    answer:"Mercury"
}]}},
{
  category:{
    quizTitle:"This Quiz based on Universe and solar system",
    quizDetail:"Welcome to interesting Easy General Knowledge Questions and Answers Quiz. It has Multiple Choice Questions with a single correct answer.",
    quiz : [{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"The day on which the Sun ’ s direct rays cross the celestial equator is called:",
      optionOne:"The Aphelion",
      optionTwo:"The Solstice",
      optionThree:"The Equinox",
      optionFour:"The Ecliptic",
      answer:"The Equinox"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"Who invented the telescope ?",
      optionOne:"Johannes Kepler",
      optionTwo:"Galileo",
      optionThree:"Hypatia",
      optionFour:"Hans Lippershey",
      answer:"Galileo"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"Which of these objects is the farthest from the Sun ?",
      optionOne:"Saturn",
      optionTwo:"Neptune",
      optionThree:"90377 Sedna",
      optionFour:"Kuiper belt",
      answer:"Neptune"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"What term describes the alignment of three celestial bodies?",
      optionOne:"syzygy",
      optionTwo:"sizzle",
      optionThree:"symbology",
      optionFour:"suzerainty",
      answer:"syzygy"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"What is the smallest planet in the solar system by mass?",
      optionOne:"Earth",
      optionTwo:"Mercury",
      optionThree:"Mars",
      optionFour:"Jupiter",
      answer:"Mercury"
    }]}},
 { category:{
    quizTitle:"This Quiz based on Astronomy and Facts about space !",
    quizDetail:"Welcome to another interesting Hard General Knowledge Questions and Answers Quiz. It has Multiple Choice Questions with a single correct answer.",
    quiz : [{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"The day on which the Sun ’ s direct rays cross the celestial equator is called:",
      optionOne:"The Aphelion",
      optionTwo:"The Solstice",
      optionThree:"The Equinox",
      optionFour:"The Ecliptic",
      answer:"The Equinox"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"Who invented the telescope ?",
      optionOne:"Johannes Kepler",
      optionTwo:"Galileo",
      optionThree:"Hypatia",
      optionFour:"Hans Lippershey",
      answer:"Galileo"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"Which of these objects is the farthest from the Sun ?",
      optionOne:"Saturn",
      optionTwo:"Neptune",
      optionThree:"90377 Sedna",
      optionFour:"Kuiper belt",
      answer:"Neptune"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"What term describes the alignment of three celestial bodies?",
      optionOne:"syzygy",
      optionTwo:"sizzle",
      optionThree:"symbology",
      optionFour:"suzerainty",
      answer:"syzygy"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"What is the smallest planet in the solar system by mass?",
      optionOne:"Earth",
      optionTwo:"Mercury",
      optionThree:"Mars",
      optionFour:"Jupiter",
      answer:"Mercury"
  }]}},
 { category:{
    quizTitle:"Quiz for children's under age 10 to 15 yrs old",
    quizDetail:"Perfect for kids, this quiz will get you thinking about the fascinating topics of space and astronomy. Quizzes have become a more popular tool !",
    quiz : [{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"The day on which the Sun ’ s direct rays cross the celestial equator is called:",
      optionOne:"The Aphelion",
      optionTwo:"The Solstice",
      optionThree:"The Equinox",
      optionFour:"The Ecliptic",
      answer:"The Equinox"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"Who invented the telescope ?",
      optionOne:"Johannes Kepler",
      optionTwo:"Galileo",
      optionThree:"Hypatia",
      optionFour:"Hans Lippershey",
      answer:"Galileo"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"Which of these objects is the farthest from the Sun ?",
      optionOne:"Saturn",
      optionTwo:"Neptune",
      optionThree:"90377 Sedna",
      optionFour:"Kuiper belt",
      answer:"Neptune"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"What term describes the alignment of three celestial bodies?",
      optionOne:"syzygy",
      optionTwo:"sizzle",
      optionThree:"symbology",
      optionFour:"suzerainty",
      answer:"syzygy"
  },{ 
      id: uuidv4(),
      question:"What is the smallest planet in the solar system by mass?",
      optionOne:"Earth",
      optionTwo:"Mercury",
      optionThree:"Mars",
      optionFour:"Jupiter",
      answer:"Mercury"
  }]}},
];
